oké
give the camera a smile here
this here ó
has already generated a doubt that this guy will do
this is already a connection point
you look at the camera
you give a smile
you back
starts playing
looked looking
O looked at the guitar
looked at the camera
very important
when you deliver your art
you finish
now it's worth
tamo together people
he didn't get rid
listen to some of his songs we go to his show
ok
it is
seventh
for the first time here is a big deal on the hotplay show
something something historical
in my life right
for the first time
valeu
since i know
i asked god why i
at that time there were never
thought i could get here at worship
and walk
meet a and go to a show
I'm away
very expensive
and i'll never forget it here
because it's the first time
and i have to tell someone this
I think the parade you feel is cool.
and we need all of us
but don't think that was an experience
only one you had
and yes a beginning
someone here is giving you nothing man
you who conquered
that's a point you have to have
proud of you
from your heart
is on
no choice brother
has moment
it was supposed to be your time
for me it's a gift
is on
thank you saw
thank you